[
    {
        "question": "Who created Superman?",
        "answers": [
            "Jack Kirby & Bob Kane",
            "Bob Kane & Joe Shuster",
            "Joe Shuster & Jerry Siegel",
            "Jerry Siegel & Stan Lee"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "timeLimit": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the dimensional plane where Kryptonian criminals were exiled for their crimes?",
        "answers": [
            "No Man's Land",
            "Phantom Zone",
            "Zimbardo's Prison",
            "Bizarro World"
        ],
        "correct": 1,
        "timeLimit": 35
    },
{
        "question": "Where did Luke and Obi-Wan met Han Solo?",
        "answers": [
            "Mos Espa",
            "Mos Eisley",
            "Tosche Station",
            "Anchorhead"
        ],
        "correct": 1,
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Princess Leia is the Senator for which planet?",
        "answers": [
            "Naboo",
            "Coruscant",
            "Yavin 4",
            "Alderaan"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main object that everyone is looking for in \"Raiders of the Lost Ark\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Ark of the Covenant",
            "Holy Grail",
            "Noah's Ark",
            "Magic Rocks"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In C++, in what order do the constructors get called?",
        "answers": [
            "Parent to child",
            "Child to parent",
            "Peer to peer"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "timeLimit": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "What keyword makes a member visible to inherited classes and hidden from others?",
        "answers": [
            "private",
            "protected",
            "public"
        ],
        "correct": 1,
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Which cannot be used for computing rotation?",
        "answers": [
            "Translation",
            "Matrix",
            "Quaternion"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "The “namespace” keyword helps solve what problem?",
        "answers": [
            "Template class specialization",
            "Declaring pure-virtual classes",
            "Avoids collisions between global identifiers"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Why would we pass a variable to a function by reference?",
        "answers": [
            "Avoid memory allocation and guarantees an initialized object",
            "Offer a chance for “pointer arithmetic”",
            "Protects against changes to the variable"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Order the following in terms of performance from fastest to slowest:",
        "answers": [
            "New, addition, square root",
            "Square root, addition, new",
            "Addition, square root, new"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you normalize a 3D vector?",
        "answers": [
            "Set x, y, and z to one",
            "Add x squared to y squared to z squared, then square root that sum",
            "Divide each of its x, y, z components by its length"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "timeLimit": 0
    }
]